드디어 결혼했군!
Oh, my God, we did it!
바로 여기서 결혼했지!
We just got married. Right there!
결혼반지야?
Is that your ring?
시작이 좋군
We're off to a good start.
- 정말 임신하지 않았어?
- 확실해
-And, you sure you're not pregnant?
-Yeah. I'm sure.
아이를 가질 준비가 됐으면
올라가자
But if you're ready to have kids
we got a room upstairs.
파티는 안중에도 없어
I mean, I'll blow off
this party right now. I'll do it!
멋진 결혼식이었어
Okay, you guys,
that ceremony was so beautiful.
완벽했어?
비디오를 보면 안 될까?
Was it?! Was it perfect?!
Is it too soon to see the video?!
잠깐만 기다려 봐
절친한 친구들이 결혼했잖아
Can we just please take a moment?
Our two best friends just got married.
이런 기쁨을 나눈단 건
우리의 축복이라고
We are so blessed to be able
to share in this incredible joy.
백 번 옳은 소리야
That is so true.
지금이라도 치킨에서
스테이크로 바꿔도 돼?
Mon, is it too late to switch
from chicken to steak?
진심으로 축하해
너흰 행운아들이야
I'm so happy for you guys.
And you are both so lucky!
상대의 이름도
헷갈리지 않았잖아
I mean, you both said the right names
취한 사람도 없었고
And nobody was drunk.
맞아
Okay.
게이도 없었지
And nobody was gay.
첫 결혼이잖아
And on your first try.
프렌즈 시즌 8
'결혼 피로연'
아주 좋아요
필름을 갈아 끼울게요
Great. Great.
Just give me a sec to change film.
내가 알기엔 이르지만
경사가 아닐 수 없어
I know I'm not supposed to know,
but I do and I'm so excited for you.
- 뭔 소리야?
- 모니카가 임신했어
-What's going on?
-Monica's pregnant.
결혼한 진짜 이유는
따로 있었군
Oh, my God. Is that why
you guys had to get married?
- 임신하지 않았어
- 헤엄을 못 치는군
-Guys, I'm not pregnant.
-Oh, slow swimmers?
임신하지 않았다고?
What?! What do you mean?
You're not pregnant?
- 임신했다고 소문냈어?
- 아니
-You didn't tell anybody I was, did you?
-No.
금방 올게
I'll be right back.
오랫동안 찍어야 돼요
You. Take a lot of pictures.
모니카와 군인분을 찍죠
Why don't we get a shot of Monica
and the bloody soldier.
조이, 옷을 갈아입어
About that, Joey, you have
to change before the party.
- 갈아입을 옷이 없어
- 어떻게든 구해 와
-I can't. I don't have any other clothes here.
-Find some, please.
그 복장은 프랑스에서
전사한 군인 같아
Anything that doesn't say,
"I died tragically in France."
- 알았어!
- 아무나 껴안지 마
-Fine!
-And be careful who you hug, okay?
네 피가 옷에 묻어
아버지께서 울고 계셔
My father's upstairs in tears
because you got blood on his dress.
이번에는 신부 들러리들도
함께 찍어요
Why don't we see the bride and the groom,
and the bridesmaids.
왜 임신하지 않았다고
얘기했어?
Hey, Mon, why'd you tell the guys
that you weren't pregnant?
- 사실이니까
- 네 임신검사기를 봤어
-Because I'm not.
-We found your tests.
네가 아니라면...
If you're not pregnant..
임신한 사람은 나로군
it's because I am.
무슨 말이야?
What are you talking about?
난 홀몸이 아니라고
Yes, I am with child.
네가 주인공이라서
잠자코 있었어
I didn't want to say anything
because it's your day.
- 분위기 망치면 안 되잖아
- 그래서 내가 임신했다고 말했어?
-I didn't wanna steal your thunder.
-So you told people I was pregnant?
내가 이런 대화를
기억하고 있어야 돼?
Does this look like a conversation
I want to remember?
- 아기의 아빠는?
- 그래, 누구야?
-Who's the father?
-Yeah.
비밀이야
I can't say.
- 왜?
- 어째서?
-Why?
-Why not?
유명인이라서
말해 줄 수가 없거든
I can't say because he's famous.
대체 누군데 그래?
Oh, my God. Who is it?
더 궁금하잖아
Phoebe, come on, you have to tell us.
알았어, 말할게
제임스 브롤린이야
Okay, okay, it's James Brolin.
그 남자가 아기의 아빠야
James Brolin is the father of my baby.
바브라 스트라이센드의
남편?
As in Barbra Streisand's husband
James Brolin?
뭐라고?
What?!
그런 말은 안 했는데
Well, he never said that to me.
모니카, 챈들러와 들러리를
찍을게요
Monica, if you step away,
we'll get Chandler and the bridesmaids.
독사진은 안 돼요?
How about just the bridesmaids?
신랑인 내가 빠지면 안 되지
I am the groom.
I was told it was a big deal.
- 그래
- 맞아
-It is.
-Yeah.
맙소사
Oh, my God.
고마웠어
감당할 엄두가 안 나
Thank you for that.
I can't deal with the stress quite yet.
그래서 모니카에게 뒤집어씌웠어?
Instead you told me
Monica was pregnant?
난 너한테 들었어
You said she was.
I didn't disagree with you.
치사해
Sneaky.
김치!
Smile, ladies!
- 웬 제임스 브롤린?
- 그러게 말야
-By the way, James Brolin?
-I know.
그와 에드 베글리 주니어밖에
떠오르지 않더라고
I could only think of two names:
him and Ed Begley Jr.
- 그래서 게이를 빼고...
- 에드 베글리 주니어는 게이가 아냐
-Then I remembered he's gay, so..
-Ed Begley Jr. is not gay.
정말?
Really?
축하한다
Congratulations!
때맞춰 날짜를 잡았구나
Look who's married!
And just in time too, I hear.
네? 로스!
What? Ross!
네가 대신 수습해 주면
난...
So if you've got this all under control,
I'm just gonna..
우리가 얼마나 기쁜지
넌 모를 거다
I just wanted you to know
that you have made us happier
정말이지...
You have given us more joy..
임신 안 했어요
I'm not pregnant.
뭐?
What?
임신이 아니라고요
I'm not pregnant.
그렇구나
Oh, well.
그래도 결혼은 했잖아요
But I did still get married today.
알게 뭐람
Whatever.
감사합니다
Thank you very much.
신사 숙녀 여러분
주인공을 소개드립니다
Ladies and gentlemen, it gives me
great pleasure to introduce to you:
챈들러 빙 부부입니다
Mr. and Mrs. Chandler Bing.
- 선물을 준비했어
- 네 주머니에 손을 넣으라고?
-Before we go out there, I got a present.
-I'm not gonna put my hand in your pocket.
- 아니, 댄스 교습을 받았어
- 뭐?
-No. I've been taking dancing lessons.
-What?
이 순간을 위해 6주 동안
교습을 받았단 말야
For the last six weeks. I wanted this
to be a moment you'd never forget.
정말 멋지다
That is so sweet.
부부로서 처음으로
춤을 춰 볼까?
So would you care to join me
in our first dance as husband and wife?
좋아
Yes.
- 왜 그래?
- 새 신발이라서 미끄러워
-What's the matter?
-It's these new shoes, they're all slippery.
- 출 수 있겠어?
- 대충
-Are you gonna be able to do this?
-Not well.
쳐다보는 사람이 없어서
다행이군
Well, the good news is,
I don't think anyone's looking at us.
얘기할 준비가 됐어?
So are you ready to talk about it?
아니
No.
지금은?
Now?
아니야!
No!
- 그럼 다른 얘기를 하자
- 고마워
-We'll talk about something else then.
-Thank you.
아빠가 누구야?
Who's the father?
그에게도 말을 못 했어
Honey, I haven't told him yet..
그래서 남들에게도
말해 줄 수가 없어
so, until I do, I don't think
I should tell anybody else.
그래, 그래야지
That's fine. That's fair.
- 태그야?
- 피비!
-Is it Tag?
-Phoebe!
미안해, 그만 할게
Okay, I'm sorry. I'll stop.
로스야? 맞지?
Is it Ross? It's Ross, isn't it?
- 그럼 조이구나!
- 그만 좀 해
-Oh, my God, it's Joey!
-Stop it. Okay?
그에게 먼저 말해야 돼
I am not gonna tell you
until I tell him.
남자인 건 알았어
At least we know it's a him.
세상에나
Oh, sweet Lord.
미안해, 상점에 갔는데
I'm sorry, okay?
I went down to the gift shop.
이 옷과 목욕가운밖에 없어
하지만 중요하지 않아
It was either this or a bathrobe.
What's more important:
내 옷차림이 뭐가 중요해?
The way I'm dressed,
or being with you today?
들은 척도 안 하겠어
이봐!
Honey, I'm not gonna even pretend
I was listening. Hey! Hey!
처음 뵙겠습니다
모니카의 오빠, 로스예요
I'm Ross, I don't believe we met.
I'm Monica's older brother.
식당에서 같이 일하는
모나라고 해요
Hi, I'm Mona from her restaurant.
반가워요
식당에서 일하는 모나!
Hello, Mona from her restaurant.
이름이 참 예쁘군요
Mona. What a beautiful name.
난 마음에 안 들어요
You think so?
I always kind of hated it.
왜요? 모나리자도 있고...
Come on! Mona Lisa.
모나...
Mona...
클레클라킨
Llegglachen.
저명한 식물학자죠
The famous botanist.
지금은...
죽었지만...
Oh, no, she's..
Well, she's dead now, but..
한때는 식물세계를
주름잡던 사람이었어요
Supposedly she was once
quite the hottie of the plant world.
정말요?
Really?
- 처음 들어 봐요
- 린다 클레클라킨...
-See, I never knew about her.
-Linda Llegglachen..
몇 번 테이블이죠?
So, what table are you at?
똑같군요
Me too.
내 이름을 좋아하는 사람과
앉겠군요
Good. Now there'll be someone there
who likes my name.
그럼요
Yes, there will.
몰리 길버트, 당신은
1번 테이블로 옮겨요
Guess what, Molly Gilbert. You've
just been bumped up to table one.
6번 테이블엔
내가 대신 앉아야겠어요
And if it's all right with you,
I'll take your place at table six.
마틴 클레클라킨
Martin Llegglachen.
좋아요, 팔을 더 굽히고
정면을 쳐다봐요
That's better. Now, just bend your arms
a little bit. Now look straight ahead.
엉덩이를 이용해서
휘둘러 봐요
This time I want you
to really put your ass into it.
왜 이렇게 미끄러워?
Who's slippery now?
포크로 긁고 있으면
기분이 좋지 않아?
Isn't that just the best feeling?
Rubbing a fork on the bottom of your shoe?
얘야, 엄마의 애인이
도착했단다
Chandler, darling, look,
my date has finally arrived.
데니스 필립스라고 해
우리 아들, 챈들러야
I'd like you to meet Dennis Phillips.
Dennis, this is my son, Chandler.
- 축하하네
- 고마워요
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
데니스는 친구이면서...
Dennis is a dear old friend..
훌륭한 애인이란다
and a fantastic lover.
귀에서 피가 나나요?
Are my ears bleeding?
신경쓰지 말아요
원래 수줍음이 많아요
Don't mind Chandler.
He's always been shy.
맞아요
Oh, you're right.
어머니를 기쁘게 해 줘서
감사합니다
Bravo, Dennis.
Thanks for pleasing my mother so.
오디션 심사 때문에
예식을 보지 못했네
I'm so sorry I missed the ceremony.
I was stuck at auditions.
새 뮤지컬의 감독을 맡았지
Yes, Dennis is directing
a new Broadway show.
조이 트리비아니라고 해요
I don't believe we've met.
Joey Tribbiani.
- 데니스 필립스예요
- 선생님의 작품을 좋아해요
-Dennis Phillips.
-I've admired your work for years.
- 대단한 작품들이에요
- 고맙네
-You've done some really amazing stuff.
-Thank you.
난 뭐 좀 마셔야겠어
If you'll excuse me,
I'm gonna go get myself a drink.
금방 올게
I'll be back in a moment.
이제 됐어요
Okay. You stop.
데니스 필립이라니
어떻게 만나셨어요?
Dennis Phillips. That's great.
How did you guys meet?
- 웃기게 만났지
- "하하"예요, "팡팡"이에요?
-Well, it's a funny story.
-Funny, "ha-ha"? Or funny:
자리에 앉아 주시면
저녁식사를 시작하겠습니다
Thank you. If everyone will please
take your seats, dinner will be served.
- 6번이 아니었나요?
- 9번이에요
-I thought you were at table six.
-No. Nine.
아까는...
이렇게 보여 줘서...
See, before, when you showed it to me,
you held it that way..
잘못 봤군요
which was misleading.
안녕
Hello.
어머니를 통해서
내 이력서를 주면 안 돼?
Will you see if your mom can give
my resume to Dennis Phillips?
두 사람은 남자화장실에서
한 칸을 전세냈어
Well, they've kind of locked themselves in
one of the men's room stalls right now.
나오면 말해줄게
Perhaps when they get out.
브로드웨이에 진출만 하면
탄탄대로거든
If I could get in a Broadway show,
then I would've done it all.
영화, TV, 연극...
Film, television and theater.
라디오만 빼고 말야
못생긴 사람들 몫이니까
The only thing left would be radio.
But that's just for ugly people.
- 신발치수가 어떻게 돼?
- 11이나 11 반
-What size shoes do you wear?
-Eleven, 11½.
춤추기가 힘들어서 그런데
구두 좀 빌려줘
My shoes give me a problem on the
dance floor. Can I borrow your boots?
어디 뒀는지 잘 모르겠어
I don't really even know
where I left those.
- 그게 11이나 돼?
- 그래, 7이다!
-Those aren't 11 ½.
-Okay, fine, I'm a 7!
발은 작지만 나머진 훌륭해
보여줄까?
I have surprisingly small feet.
But the rest of me is good. I'll show you.
난 역시 라디오가 딱이야
Who am I kidding?
I belong in radio.
- 피비가 임신했다니 놀라워
- 그 얘긴 나중에 하자
-Can you believe Phoebe got pregnant?
-Let's not talk about that right now.
- 큰 사건이잖아
- 네 결혼식보다?
-This is so huge.
-Sure, but as big as your wedding?
결혼식보다 큰 사건은 없지
Of course not. Nothing is.
우리니까 하는 말인데
Between me and you,
in this day and age..
멍청하게 임신을 하다니
how dumb do you have to be
to get pregnant?
모든 사람들이
도구를 착용하긴 하지만
Sometimes you can do everything right.
Everyone wears what they're supposed to..
한 놈이 뚫고 갈 수가 있어
and one of those little guys
just gets through.
- 어떻게?
- 연장을 쓰나 보지
-How?
-I don't know. Maybe they have tools.
얘기해 봤는데
아이를 낳기로 했대
Well, I talked to her, and she's
definitely gonna have the baby.
혼자서 기르겠다는군
She said she's gonna
raise it on her own.
- 힘든 결정이구나
- 어쩌면
-Well, maybe that's really brave.
-Maybe.
얼마나 힘든 일인지
알았으면 좋겠어
I just hope she realizes how hard
it's gonna be.
심각하게 생각해 보지
않았나 봐
Maybe she hasn't really thought it
through that much.
생각할게 한두 개가 아냐
Well, there's a lot to think about.
경제적으로 어떡하려고?
또 직장은 어떡하고?
How is she gonna handle this financially?
How is she gonna juggle work?
앞으로 18년간 데이트를
한 번도 못 할 거라고
Does she realize she's not gonna have
a date again for the next, like, 18 years?
글쎄
I don't know.
괜찮니?
Are you okay?
피비가 걱정돼서 그래
임산부 피비 말야
I'm just thinking about Phoebe.
Poor, knocked-up Phoebe.
- 샴페인?
- 네, 고마워요
-Champagne?
-Oh, yes! Thank you very much.
원래 프랑스 사람들은
이렇게 마셔
That's actually how the French drink it.
방금 제임스 브롤린과
통화하고 왔어
Well, I just got off the phone
with my lover James Brolin.
- 그러셔?
- 여가수의 남편이 맞다는군
-Oh, really?
-Apparently, he is married to some singer.
나와 결혼하기 위해서
그녀와 갈라서겠대
But he said he'd leave her for me.
And I said, "James Brolin, are you sure?"
- 그가 말하길...
- 레이첼이 임신했다고?
-James Brolin said..
-Rachel's the one who's pregnant?
뭐?
What?!
알게 뭐야?
Why bother?
- 기분이 어때?
- 나도 모르겠어
-How do you feel?
-I don't know how I feel.
너무 갑작스런 일이야
결정하기도 싫은 문제고
This is all happening so fast. I have to make
all these decisions that I don't wanna make.
이것 좀 치워 줘
Someone just take this away from me!
- 임신이 아닐 수도 있어
- 뭐?
-Calm down. Maybe you're not pregnant.
-What?!
나도 임신했을 때
검사를 세 번이나 했어
When I got pregnant with the triplets,
I took that test, like, three times.
거짓양성일지도 몰라
확실히 소변을 묻혔어?
Yes. Maybe it's a false positive.
Are you sure you peed on the stick right?
다른 방법도 있어?
How many ways are there to do that?
검사결과가 100퍼센트
맞진 않단 거야
I'm just saying, don't freak out
until you're 100 percent sure.
알았어, 집에 가서
다시 해 볼게
All right, I'll take it again
when I get home.
그때까지 기다리지 뭐
I can wait until then.
정말 멋진 파티야
언제 끝나?
Oh, this is such a good party.
How late does it go till?
- 먼저 들어가
- 네 결혼식이잖아
-You gotta take it now.
-No, this your wedding.
마음이 편치 않잖아
결혼선물이라고 생각해
You're not gonna be able to have fun
until we know. Do it as a present to me.
고마워
Okay, thank you.
- 내가 하나 사 올게
- 너흰 좋은 친구야
-I'll run out and get you one.
-You girls are so great.
- 잠깐, 아빠는 누구야?
- 말할 수 없대
-Wait a minute. Who's the father?
-She won't tell us.
결혼선물로 가르쳐 줘
Come on! It's my wedding.
That could be my present!
- 소변 보는게 선물이잖아
- 이래서 등록을 해야 돼
-I just gave you peeing on a stick.
-See, this is why you register.
의자에서 나는 소리야
난 아니라고!
It was the chair again. Okay?
I'm not doing it!
원래 자리로 가면 안 돼요?
Dad. Can't you go back to your table?
몰리 길버트는 다 자란
연어요리를 즐기고 있단다
No. Apparently little Molly Gilbert is
enjoying her grown-up salmon en croute.
이건...
내가 아니라니까
Look, I don't..
You know what?
- 춤출래요?
- 그럼요
-Would you like to dance?
-Sure.
좋아요
Great.
- 겔러 박사님
- 방귀소리가 아니야!
-Dr. Geller.
-I wasn't farting!
우리가 하던 놀이예요
A little game from our table.
저랑 춤추실래요?
Dr. Geller, will you dance with me?
지금은 곤란해
이분과 춰야 하거든
Maybe later. Right now,
I'm about to dance with this lady.
이분이 양보하시면
너와 먼저 추도록 할게
Unless this lady wouldn't mind
letting you go first.
먼저 추렴
자상하시군요
I'd be happy to.
You are very sweet.
그럼요
Yes, I am.
특별한 자세로 추자
네 발을 밟고 춰
In fact, let's try my special way.
You can dance on my feet.
- 좋아요
- 이리 오렴
-Sure.
-Yeah? Hop on.
예쁜 언니가 보고 있니?
계속 춰라
Is the pretty lady looking?
Keep dancing.
아무도 모를 거야
And the world will never know.
데니스에게 말해 봤어?
Did you talk to Dennis about me yet?
욕망의 세월에 대해서도
얘기했어
I told him how talented you were
and all about Days of our Lives.
그러면 어떡해?
멜로배우로 알 거라고
You don't tell a Broadway guy that!
Now he thinks I'm just a soap actor.
단순한 멜로배우가 아니지
But you're not just a soap actor.
작은 발을 가진
멜로배우잖아
You are a soap actor
with freakishly tiny feet.
그는 내 가능성을
알지 못한다고
He has no idea
what kind of range I have.
꼼짝 말고 있어
Don't move.
애기 신발을 신고
뛰는 것 같아
It's like he's running
on tiny little pegs.
- 감사합니다
- 내가 고맙지, 미란다
-Thank you.
-No, thank you, Miranda.
- 멜린다예요
- 그래
-Melinda.
-All right.
- 참 귀여웠어요
- 보고 있었어요?
-How cute was that?
-Oh, were you watching?
저도 추고 싶어요
Can I go next?
그럼, 올라타렴
Of course you can. Hop on.
이 다음은 내가 올라가겠어요
Okay, but I get to hop on after her.
- 일진이 좋군
- 네?
-I am so gonna score.
-What?
머리핀이 이쁘다고
I like your bow.
모니카와 챈들러를 위해
축배를 들고 싶습니다
I'd like to propose a toast
to Monica and Chandler..
세계 최고로 멋진 부부이자
제 절친한 친구들이죠
the greatest couple in the world,
and my best friends.
처음 소식을 들었을 때
전 분노했습니다
When I first found out they were
getting married, I was a little angry.
"왜 그들을 제게서
빼앗아 가십니까?"
I was like, "Why, God? Why?
How can you take them away from me!"
전 그들과의 행복한 추억을
되새겨 봤어요
But then I thought back over all our
memories together. Some happy memories.
슬픈 추억도 있었죠
And there were some sad memories.
죄송합니다
I'm sorry.
무서운 추억도요
And some scared memories.
그리고 언제나 친구로
남을 거란 사실을 깨달았죠
And then I realized
I'll always be their friend.
여러 사투리를 구사하고
Their friend who can speak
in many dialects..
부분 노출장면을 찍을
의향이 있는 친구 말예요
and has training in stage combat
and is willing to do partial nudity.
참, 행복한 부부를 위하여
To the happy couple.
- 감사합니다
- 참 즐거웠다
-Thank you.
-That was very nice, Ashley.
- 또 출까요?
- 아니
-Can we do it again?
-No, no.
- 내 차례인가요?
- 저예요
-So, is it my turn now?
-I'm next.
- 난 괜찮아요
- 정말이에요?
-That's okay, you can dance with her first.
-Are you sure?
- 이름이 뭐니?
- 거트예요
-So, what's your name?
-Gert.
예쁘구나
That's pretty.
뭐 하는 거냐?
What are you doing there, Gert?
다른 애들처럼
발을 밟고 추려고요
Dancing on your feet
like the other girls did it.
올라와라, 거트
Hop on, Gert.
- 왜 안 움직여요?
- 애쓰고 있단다
-Why aren't you moving your feet?
-I'm trying.
더 빨리 움직여요
너무 느리잖아요
Faster. You're not going fast enough.
내가 올라가야겠는걸
Maybe I should stand on your feet!
혹시 제 축배를 들으셨나요?
So did you happen to catch
my toast up there?
- 날 보라고 한 건가?
- 모두를 위한 거죠
-Oh, my God. That was for my benefit?
-There was a little something for everyone.
- 새로운 배우를 선발 중이시죠?
- 자네는 어울리지 않네
-I know you're casting for this new show.
-I don't think you're right for this project.
천만에요
You're wrong.
전 어떤 배역이라도
소화할 수 있답니다
Whatever it is, I can do it.
If you didn't see it up there, just try me.
중국인 배역인데
자네가 할 수 있겠나?
It's an all Chinese cast.
Can you be Chinese?
- 그렇다면...
- 맙소사, 관두게!
-Well, I'm not proud of this, but..
-Oh, my God. Please don't!
- 춤추러 갈까?
- 모래밭으로 변했어?
-Ready to get back to the dance floor?
-Did it turn into sand?
- 나와, 내가 좋아하는 노래야
- 안 돼
-Come on, I love this song. You'll be fine.
-No. No, I won't.
왜 교습을 받았는 줄 알아?
Do you know why
I took all those lessons?
하객들이 모인 자리에서
서투른 멍청이와
I didn't want you to be embarrassed
to be seen on the dance floor..
창피당하게 하기 싫어서
with some clumsy idiot.
절대로 창피하지 않아
Oh, sweetie,
you could never embarrass me.
사실은 창피해 죽겠지만
참을 수 있어
Okay, you could easily embarrass me.
But it doesn't matter, all right?
우린 부부잖아
I married you.
네가 무슨 짓을 해도
난 창피하지 않다고
No matter what you do,
I'm gonna come home with you, okay?
내 결혼식날 밤
내 남편과 춤출 거야
So I'm gonna dance on my wedding night
with my husband. Come on.
그 신발가게에는 다시는
가지 않을 거야
But I'll tell you, that's the last time I buy
shoes at the Slippery Fun Shoe store.
발을 최대한 움직이지 마
Just try not to move your feet at all.
잘하네
There you go.
- 자네를 고소하겠네
- 왜요?
-I'm gonna have you arrested.
-Why?
이건 내 춤이란 말야!
You stole my moves!
춤솜씨가 대단하구나
Oh, Chandler, you're quite the dancer!
- 감사합니다, 겔러 부인
- 어머니라고 불러
-Thanks, Mrs. Geller.
-Oh, come on, you can call me Mom.
정말요?
Really?
그러죠
I will.
미안해요, 어머니
Sorry, Mom.
- 아직 멀었어?
- 30초
-How much longer?
-30 seconds.
알았어
Thirty seconds, okay..
결과 나왔어?
Did I miss it?
만일 양성으로 나오면
우리가...
I want you to know that
if it's positive, we're gonna..
- 그래, 알아
- 그래
-I know. I know.
-You do. Okay.
시간 됐어
It's time.
확인해 봐
Go ahead, Rach.
볼 자신이 없으니까
대신 봐 줘
Wait. You know what? I can't look at it.
Somebody else tell me.
음성이야
It's negative.
- 뭐?
- 음성반응이야
-What?
-It's negative.
그렇군
Well, there you go.
정말 다행이군
듣던 중 반가운 소식이야
That is.. That's great.
That is really great, great news.
난...
You know, because the whole..
경제적 능력도 없고...
not being ready and, kind of,
the financial aspects, all that..
내가 원했던 결과야
천만다행이지
This is so just the way
that this was supposed to be.
잘된 일이야
Then, great.
이렇게 바보같다니
God, this is so stupid.
괜히 걱정하고 있었잖아
How can I be upset
over something I never had?
- 음성 맞지?
- 아냐, 양성이야
-It's negative?
-No, it's positive.
- 뭐?
- 음성이 아니라 양성이라고
-What?
-It's not negative, it's positive.
- 확실해?
- 아깐 거짓말이었어
-Are you sure?
-Yeah, I lied before.
- 이제 네 속마음을 알았어
- 간떨어질 뻔했어
-Now you know how you really feel about it.
-That's a risky little game.
아기를 낳을 거야?
Are you really gonna do this?
응
Yeah.
낳아서 길러야지
I'm gonna have a baby.
아기를 낳을 거야
낳을 거라고!
I'm gonna have a baby!
- 아빠는?
- 아직 말할 수 없어
-With who?
-No, it's still not the time.
빠른 노래가 나오는 걸
미처 몰랐어
I just didn't see the fast song coming.
방에 가서 발을 담그면
한결 나아질 거야
Don't talk, we'll get you up to your room,
soak your feet. You'll be okay.
- 고마워
- 착하시군요!
-Thank you.
-That is so sweet!
이렇게 착한 남자는
흔치 않아요
No, I mean it. There are so few
genuinely nice guys out there.
그러게 말이에요
제가 유일한 한 명이죠
Tell me about it. I feel like I'm
holding down the fort by myself.
- 조이라고 했죠?
- 맞아요
-It's Joey, right?
-Yeah.
잠깐만요!
Wait a minute! No!
착한 건 나라고요!
I'm the nice one!
밤새 애들과 춤춘 사람은
바로 나라고요
I'm the one that danced
with the kids all night. I..
발 한번 작군!
How small are your feet?!